#https://opentdb.com/- open trivia database to access database
question_data = [
    {"category": "Entertainment: Music", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "The music group Daft Punk got their name from a negative review they recieved.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Film", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "The film &quot;2001: A Space Odyssey&quot; was released on December 31st, 2000.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Film", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "Matt Damon played an astronaut stranded on an extraterrestrial planet in both of the movies Interstellar and The Martian.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Film", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "The 2010 film &quot;The Social Network&quot; is a biographical drama film about MySpace founder Tom Anderson.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "Big the Cat is a playable character in &quot;Sonic Generations&quot;.", "correct_answer": "False",
     "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"category": "Geography", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
                                      "question": "Ottawa is the capital of Canada.", "correct_answer": "True",
                                      "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Music", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "Daft Punk originated in France.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime & Manga", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "In the &quot;To Love-Ru&quot; series, Golden Darkness is sent to kill Lala Deviluke.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "History", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "The French Kingdom helped the United States gain their independence over Great Britain during the Revolutionary War.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Science & Nature", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "Not including false teeth; A human has two sets of teeth in their lifetime.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}
]
